tiresplus.com 2019-05-25

# Tires Plus Privacy Policy | Tires Plus

Tires Plus thanks you for accessing or using this web site (the "Site"). Tires Plus wants to assure you that we respect your privacy. We know that trust is the key to any successful business relationship. The following Privacy Policy describes Tires Plus’s commitment to protecting your personal information.

Use of this Site constitutes your consent to the collection and use of the information as described below in this Privacy Policy. If Tires Plus changes this Privacy Policy, Tires Plus will update this page of the Site so that you will be aware of any changes to this policy. Tires Plus encourages you to review this Privacy Policy from time to time so you will know if the Privacy Policy has been changed or updated.

This Privacy Policy explains how Tires Plus collects, uses and discloses your personal information. This Privacy Policy also explains the steps Tires Plus has taken to ensure that your personal information is secure. Finally, this Privacy Policy explains your choices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information.

THE SITE INCLUDES LINKS TO THE WEBSITES OF THIRD PARTIES. WE PROVIDE THESE LINKS AS A CONVENIENCE TO OUR USERS. THE INCLUSION OF ANY LINK DOES NOT IMPLY TIRES PLUS TOTAL CAR CARE’S ENDORSEMENT OF ANY COMPANY, ITS WEBSITE, OR THE PRODUCTS AND SERVICES IT SELLS. PLEASE NOTE THAT TIRES PLUS TOTAL CAR CARE IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY CONTENT OR THE PRIVACY PRACTICES OF ANY WEBSITE OTHER THAN OUR OWN SITE.

THE SITE ALSO INCLUDES CERTAIN PAGES THAT ARE "FRAMED" TO PROVIDE INFORMATION FROM WEBSITES OF THIRD PARTIES. SUCH FRAMED PAGES WILL BE IDENTIFIED ON THE PAGE AND THE PAGE OWNER IDENTIFIED. WE PROVIDE THESE FRAMED PAGES AS A CONVENIENCE TO OUR USERS. PLEASE NOTE THAT TIRES PLUS TOTAL CAR CARE IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY CONTENT OR THE PRIVACY PRACTICES OF ANY FRAMED PAGES. THE TERMS AND POLICIES OF THE PAGE OWNER IDENTIFIED ON THE FRAMED PAGE WILL CONTROL.

## Information Collection and Use.

### **1\. Information Collection.**

Tires Plus may collect information from you at several different points and in different ways on this Site. Tires Plus will ask you for your permission before Tires Plus collects any information that personally identifies you or allows Tires Plus to contact you. Tires Plus’s primary goal in collecting personal information from you is to provide you with an efficient, meaningful and customized experience. For example, Tires Plus can use your personal information to:

  * make this Site easier for you to use by not having to enter information more than once.
  * help you quickly find information and services.
  * help Tires Plus create content on this Site that is most relevant to you.
  * alert you to updated information and services offered by Tires Plus, or its affiliated companies.

**(a) Registration.** To use this Site, or certain portions or features of the Site, you may be required to first complete an online registration form. During registration you will be prompted to provide to Tires Plus certain personal information, including but not limited to your name, address, phone number and email address.

**(b) Cookies.** "Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by a user’s Internet browser on a user’s hard drive. The Site may store some information on your computer in the form of a cookie or similar file, however This Site does not use permanent cookies that contain any personally identifying information, such as your name or address. The cookies allow us to recognize you when you return to our site and may also be matched and combined with personally identifiable information collected from other sources to provide you with a customized experience that we feel will be of value to you. Most web browsers allow you to exercise control over cookie files on your computer by erasing them, blocking them, or notifying you when such a file is stored. Please take a look at your particular browser for instructions on this function. If you do elect to disable the Site’s cookies, please note that you may not be able to take full advantage of the Site.  

In addition, this site uses the following Google Analytics Advertising Features:

  * Remarketing with Google Analytics
  * Google Display Network Impression Reporting
  * Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting
  * Integrated services that require Google Analytics to collect data for advertising purposes, including the collection of data via advertising cookies and identifiers

We share the data collected using Google Analytics with a trusted set of third-party vendors and use it to help us analyze how users use our Site. Google Analytics plants a cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit this Site. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this Site is restricted by the [Google Analytics Terms of Use](http://www.google.com/analytics/tos.html) and the [Google Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html). You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to this Site by [disabling cookies](http://www.usa.gov/optout_instructions.shtml) on your browser, or following the [Google opt-out process](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

**(c) Log Files.** This Site automatically collects information pertaining to Your access. Such information may include Your Internet Protocol ("IP") address, as well as other connection and usage information for system administration and troubleshooting purposes. (An IP address indicates the location of Your computer on the Internet.) Tires Plus does not link an IP address to any personally identifiable information.

### **Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA).**

This Site is a website directed to the general public. Tires Plus does not knowingly collect information from children under 13.

### 2\. Information Use and Disclosure.

**(a) Internal Use.** Tires Plus may identify you in connection with your use of certain aspects of this Site. For example, Tires Plus may identify you by vehicle or tire ownership to provide you with information on related products and/or promotions. Tires Plus may internally use your personal information to improve Tires Plus’s marketing and promotional efforts, to improve the Site’s content and/or layout, and to determine general marketplace information about visitors to this Site.

**(b) External Use.** Tires Plus does not sell, rent, license or otherwise disclose your specific personal information to any third parties, excluding affiliated companies, without your consent. Occasionally, Tires Plus may provide statistics to outside parties about the usage of our site, but these statistics will never include any personal information about our users. Tires Plus may disclose your personal information pursuant to a court or government order. Tires Plus will share your information with affiliated companies to identify services or products that you may be of interest to you (Marketing) but you will have the opportunity to opt–out of this Marketing.

Please note that because a customer information database is customarily considered a business asset, Tires Plus reserves the right to transfer the database in a merger or sale of some or all of its company or in an action for bankruptcy. Your information will continue to be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy by the acquiring or merged company unless you are notified and provided an opportunity to change your preferences.

### **Data Security**

This Site incorporates various physical, electronic and administrative procedures to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information. Access to your personal information is restricted. Only employees who need access to your personal information to perform a specific job are granted access to your personal information. Finally, the servers where Tires Plus stores your personal information are kept in a secure environment, behind locked doors and a firewall.

WHILE TIRES PLUS HAS TAKEN COMMERCIALLY REASONABLE PRECAUTIONS TO SAFEGUARD YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION, TIRES PLUS CANNOT GUARANTEE COMPLETE SECURITY BECAUSE COMPLETE SECURITY DOES NOT PRESENTLY EXIST ON THE INTERNET.

### **Opt Out/Corrections**

Upon your request, Tires Plus will (a) remove your personal information from Tires Plus’s database (which might cancel your subscription to this Site or a portion of this Site); or (b) correct or update your personal information. You can request that Tires Plus remove, correct or update your personal information at the "Contact Us" section of this Site.

### **Updates to This Policy**

If Tires Plus decides to change or update this Privacy Policy, Tires Plus will post changes and updates on this Site so that you will always be aware of what information Tires Plus collects, uses and distributes. Tires Plus encourages you to review this Privacy Policy from time to time so you will know if the Privacy Policy has been changed or updated. If you have any questions about Tires Plus’s Privacy Policy, please use the "Contact Us" section of this Site.

* References to Tires Plus in this privacy policy includes Firestone Complete Auto Care, Hibdon Tires Plus, Wheel Works and other trade names under which Bridgestone Retail Operations operates.

**©2018 Tires Plus. All rights reserved.**

In addition, this site uses the following Google Analytics Advertising Features:

  * Remarketing with Google Analytics
  * Google Display Network Impression Reporting
  * Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting
  * Integrated services that require Google Analytics to collect data for advertising purposes, including the collection of data via advertising cookies and identifiers

We share the data collected using Google Analytics with a trusted set of third-party vendors and use it to help us analyze how users use our Site. Google Analytics plants a cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit this Site. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this Site is restricted by the [Google Analytics Terms of Use](http://www.google.com/analytics/tos.html) and the [Google Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html). You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to this Site by [disabling cookies](http://www.usa.gov/optout_instructions.shtml) on your browser, or following the [Google opt-out process](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

In addition, this site uses the following Google Analytics Advertising Features:

  * Remarketing with Google Analytics
  * Google Display Network Impression Reporting
  * Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting
  * Integrated services that require Google Analytics to collect data for advertising purposes, including the collection of data via advertising cookies and identifiers

We share the data collected using Google Analytics with a trusted set of third-party vendors and use it to help us analyze how users use our Site. Google Analytics plants a cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit this Site. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this Site is restricted by the [Google Analytics Terms of Use](http://www.google.com/analytics/tos.html) and the [Google Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html). You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to this Site by [disabling cookies](http://www.usa.gov/optout_instructions.shtml) on your browser, or following the [Google opt-out process](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

In addition, this site uses the following Google Analytics Advertising Features:

  * Remarketing with Google Analytics
  * Google Display Network Impression Reporting
  * Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting
  * Integrated services that require Google Analytics to collect data for advertising purposes, including the collection of data via advertising cookies and identifiers

We share the data collected using Google Analytics with a trusted set of third-party vendors and use it to help us analyze how users use our Site. Google Analytics plants a cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit this Site. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this Site is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Use and the Google Privacy Policy. You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to this Site by disabling cookies on your browser, or following the Google opt-out process.
